The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives a magicless boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the next Wizard King.
Though Asta's situation is practically unheard of,
there are others residing in this kingdom
who possess at least a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely use spells at all.
They make up a very small minority,
living their lives in the shadows.
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
Run away!
Help me! Help me! Help me!
On that fateful night,
the reincarnated elves came seeking vengeance.
Don't worry! I'll save you, I swear!
In the town of Tulu,
Dazu lost her husband and her mother-in-law.
With help from Bo, another resident, Dazu confronted a member of the magic parliament named Kabwe.
Kabwe despised devils, and after Domnazio delayed the trial for Nera, Asta, and Marie,
who were facing judgment for their involvement with one.
He believed the situation was being handled poorly,
which caused him to become even more enraged.
And so, the group took action.
Under the name Devil Banishers, they abducted Marie from the church in Neon.
You won't be escaping again, Servant of the Devil!
Why do you think I'm a Servant of the Devil?
The scale is tilting to darkness. We must push it toward the light!
Let's go!
Someone! Help me, please!
Please! Please, don't! Save me!
Around the same time, the Devil Banishers attempted to put Asta and Nero to sleep,
and kidnap them as well.
Nero! Let her go!
Please help me, Busta!
What do you people think you're doing?!
Get away from Asta and Nero right now!
Sealing magic! Inverse release!
I can't move my body!
Oh crap!
Am I gonna...
We're out of time, let's go!
Water creation magic!
Sea dragon!
Plant magic!
The flower on the rough side!
Water!
Now run!
Asta! Nero!
She's fast!
Sea dragon! Water ball!
Go!
Luckily, Noelle fought them off,
but the group still managed to escape with Nero in tow.
As for Asta...
Don't you dare leave without telling me who you are!
We are the Devil Banishers.
We will drive the Devil to its demise.
You won't get away!
Not until Nero is safe!
Asta...
Please wake up!
Asta!
So,
何度も何度も
目の前の今を超えるさ
涙を希望に変えていこう
七色の日常を進め
永遠に光れ
Shine like a demon
天使と悪魔が交際してく
世界は矛盾だらけさ
思い通りじゃない
そのくらいで
負ける夢はダサい
そう、何度も何度も
夢の前の今を超えるさ
何度も何度も
悪さを未来に繋げよう
七色の日常を進め
永遠に光れ
You shine like a diamond
So, we all made it
How did your mission go?
We succeeded
Where's Asta?
We apologize
Someone got in our way
I see
But still, there is some good news
He should sleep for a very long time
Doctor
I need to know that Asta is still alive
Don't worry
He's alive
Just sleeping
If that's true
Then why won't he open his eyes?
I mean
What if they put him under a spell
That causes him to sleep forever
Or something
No
I can confidently say
He's not sleeping because of a spell
That makes sense
Assuming that it's what I think it is
Let me go!
What about me suggested that I needed to be dragged here
Asta
Still snoozing, huh?
This is starting to get fishy
So, what did you mean when you said he wasn't sleeping because of a spell?
Listen Quack
You better not tell us it's a sleeping potion or something stupid like that
Actually, yes it is
Trust me, I'm as surprised as you are
Not sure who made it, but it was a ridiculously powerful concoction
But why would anybody have something like that on them?
That I don't know
In any case, he should wake up on his own after he rests for a little while longer
Thank goodness
Well, I guess we can say one thing for sure
If they put him to sleep, that probably means they weren't out to murder the kid, right?
Makes sense
First, we should find out exactly what happened
Damn it, you incompetent old hag!
This is the third time!
The third time?
That's right, the third time Marie's been put in danger
Remember?
First, these bastards took her
Then there was this whole trial thing
And now this!
That's three strikes, sister!
You're out of the game now!
Whoa, chill!
Please don't beat up the elderly
Shut your mouth, portal boy
Even if I didn't outrank you, that's just mean!
I could say that it happened while I was away from the church
But I know that's merely an excuse
Either way, I have to ask you
I have to ask you
I have to imagine
Either way
There's something you could do
That would be more proactive
Then strangling an old woman
Marie
Where are they?
Tell me
What happened to her?
It's you
Answer me right now
These mouse people calling themselves
The Devil benishers
They took her
Who the hell are they?
Then tell me what it was already!
Yeah, okay!
They said the scale is tilting to darkness and we must turn it back towards the light!
A scale, huh?
What the fuck is this?
It's poison!
That was impressive.
You're quite a skilled potion maker.
Thank you.
Those are some creepy-looking masks they got there.
I can't move my body.
Oh, crap!
Am I gonna...
That was all.
Leave it to him to fall for that obvious trick.
To tell the truth,
the spells they were using weren't all that powerful.
And maybe they were trying to be discreet so the other black bulls wouldn't pick up on their mana or something.
That explains why Henry didn't wake up when they came to the hideout.
Honestly, Yami, was that really necessary?
Not only did these evil bastards attack the base while I wasn't around,
but they had the balls to kidnap a member of my squad.
I don't know who they are, but screwing with me was the biggest mistake of their lives.
What was that noise out there?
What's wrong, sir?
Did you hear that?
I'm beginning to think doors are a foreign concept to the black bulls.
Where's my sister?
Whatever do you mean?
Has something happened to Marie?
Don't give me that!
You abducted her again!
I know you did!
You can't be serious.
Don't you dare play dumb with me!
I assure you I'm not.
Although...
You've been impertinent.
And for that you must be judged.
Gentlemen, I suggest you step back.
Yes, sir.
He did this last time.
Scale magic.
Scale regulate.
You were imprisoned once,
and it seems I'll have to put you behind bars again.
Try it and see what happens.
Mirror magic, reflect ray!
Are you all right, sir?
Casting mirror magic.
Real double.
He used a mirror to clone himself?
I already saw you pull that dumb little trick during the trial.
It's not gonna work for you this time, buddy.
It seems you've underestimated me.
On your knees!
What the hell is this?
Seize these two immediately.
Are you trying to terrorize every member of my squad, or what?
I don't care how much you despise the guy.
You can't go rogue on me like that.
What's worse, I don't recall giving you permission to hijack my wheels.
Right, wheels.
How much mana I had to waste dragging myself all the way over here.
I'm pretty sure it was easy, but okay.
Why are you two accusting him?
Because this is the second time this mole-faced freak kidnapped my sister.
Not true.
Well, who the hell did then?
I know what those guys with the masks were saying when they took her.
Something about returning the scale to the light after it tipped into darkness?
That's the exact kind of crap that you talk about.
Wait a minute.
Did you say those guys were wearing masks?
What's the difference?
Were they or not?
Well, I think so.
I wasn't there, but...
So they didn't just take Marie?
They didn't get the kid, but Nero's gone.
That means it was you!
And what led you to that conclusion?
I'm not following your logic.
First Marie, then you took Asta and Nero.
All the ones who were on trial.
You were trying to take justice into your own hands, weren't you, Kree?
Listen, I don't really care what you do to Asta and Nero.
That's kind of messed up.
Just give Marie back!
Now then, Marks, if you would show them my memories, please.
All right, I will.
In a few moments, my innocence will be proven,
and then you will pay severely for the way you've insulted me.
It's clear from his memories.
He knew nothing about any of this.
So obviously, I couldn't possibly have been involved in the situation.
Not only did you attack me, but you also accused me of a heinous crime.
I hope you're prepared to assume full responsibility.
Fine.
Do whatever you want to me.
But it'll have to wait until Marie gets back safe.
What makes you think you have any right to negotiate?
Hold on now.
The guy we saw in your memories.
You know, the one you were arguing with?
You think he would have popped in during all this ruckus.
I'm here, sir.
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry to interrupt you all,
but there's something I need Yami and his group to see.
Listen, we're a little busy.
He should be arriving any moment.
Pardon me.
It's my brother.
Remember, at the start of this mess,
we put a special communication bracelet on Asta
to keep track of his location at all times.
We're getting a signal from the town of Tu Liu in the Common Realm.
What does that mean?
Do you think somebody might have taken it off?
The only ones who even knew about that bracelet
are the people who were in the room when we did it.
And the only person I could think of
who'd be able to get that thing off
would be Nero with her sealing magic.
Perhaps she did remove it,
and now she's trying to use the signal
to broadcast her whereabouts to us.
And I bet if we find her, we'll find Marie.
Finral!
Let's go!
Yeah, so I hate to tell you this,
but I've never actually been to Tu Liu.
Guess we'll just have to travel there by broom, then.
Captain.
Allow me to accompany you.
After all, my best friend's sister is basically my sister.
Hell no!
Say that again and you're dead!
This may be a trap.
Should we really take that risk?
No one asked you, fungus head!
I don't care if it is a trap!
It's the only clue we have to go on right now!
I agree with Ghosh.
We gotta check it out.
Hold on.
I haven't finished my conversation
with this insufferable criminal yet.
Oh yeah?
Get your head out of your ass!
There's more important stuff going on here!
Yami?
Did I or did I not order the Black Bulls
to keep an eye on Nero?
You did.
They're called the Devil Banishers, yes?
Well, you can't exactly watch over her
until you get her back from them, can you?
So, Damnatio,
I'll have to ask you to withhold your judgment
for a while longer.
Is that all right?
Yes, I suppose so.
I'm counting on you, Yami.
Right.
Oh yes, and there's one more thing.
We don't have all day here.
I understand tensions are high
since one of your own has been abducted.
But remember,
this isn't like what happened
with the Magic Parliament.
With this many unknowns,
one wrong move could put your squad
in grave peril.
No need to tell me.
Enough talk.
Ready?
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
I'll go with you.
Didn't see that coming.
Why are you taking the time
to help us out
when your squad's so busy training?
We need every magic knight
in the kingdom
to help defeat the evil,
and I don't want to lose anyone
between now and then.
No more, no less.
Come on, we all know
you're just worried about your sister.
Stop trying to act like Mr. Badass.
It's getting old.
If you say one more word,
then I won't hesitate
to send you plummeting
to your death, foreigner.
So much for that fancy speech
about not wanting to lose anyone.
There it is.
It's destroyed.
It's probably one of the many areas
that were attacked
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
I'll be right there, Marie.
The signal.
Yeah, where is it?
I'm guessing that's another magic item
that prevents mana tracking
like the one I have.
Yes, just to be safe.
I doubt anyone will find us
way out here,
but it doesn't hurt.
It appears they're doing their best
to block the signal.
Do you think they know
about the bracelet?
It's possible.
Either way,
we'll be wise
to proceed with caution.
Did we really have to land
this far away from them?
Are you stupid?
I doubt it'll just be
Nero and Marie.
I'm sure the kidnappers
are keeping an eye on them.
Do you honestly think
it would work
if we barge in there
without a plan?
Gosh.
Yeah?
You got a picture
of your little sister on you?
What the hell
do you want it for?
Relax, weirdo.
We needed to ask people
if they've seen her.
That makes sense.
Mm-hmm.
I need all of them back!
We don't know
what these guys might do,
so nobody go into town alone.
Remember to watch yourselves.
Tch.
The double-G duo rides again.
You're not my sidekick.
Don't be embarrassed.
We work great together.
Let's go, Noelle.
Okay.
Well, I guess it's me and you.
You got a problem with that?
What?
No, of course not!
No one's come to help them?
We only have so many forces
we can send to make repairs.
It's strange.
This place obviously suffered
some serious damage.
And yet.
Wow.
Huh?
I know.
There's so many graves here,
you can't count them all.
Wonder how many popped up
after the big attack.
Huh?
May we don't know
No…
掴みかけたわずかな幸福が
まだ消せない誓い叫んでる 忘れないように叫んでる
泣きたいほど遠くたって 全然届かなくても
信じる君は赤い手前を向いている
だから枯れないように柄がって 描いた夢また歩き出せるきっと
僕を呼ぶ声だ
We're getting Nero and Marie back from those jerks!
Whatever it takes!
Can't seem to remember what they called themselves, though.
Let's see, it was something like...
Devil tooth pullers!
Banishers.
Devil injectors!
Nope, banishers.
Devil fourth hitters!
Banishers!
Devil nitrate passengers!
Devil news reporters!
Banishers!
Devil book publishers!
I said banishers!
Devil banishers!
For the left!
Oh, you got it.
As much as I hate to admit it,
the kingdom desperately needs Asta's help to defeat the devil.
Black Clover, page 144.
Those who wish for the devil's demise.
Someone is trying to throw the scales of justice out of balance.